Guide to the William T. Cannady Architectural Projects Records, 1956-2018 MS 577
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Articles and books, 148455
  - Houston City Magazine, March 1987; Cannady on pg. 37, 147781 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 37 no. 2, March/April 1987; Cannady (Blake Summer House) on pg. 51, 147780 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Newsletter 4, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, April 1987; Cannady on pg. 4, 147779 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - New Trends in Modern Architecture, Invitation to the opening reception of the exhibit, 10 April 1987, 147778 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - On Campus, Rice U., 20 April 1987; Cannady on pg. 6, 147777 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Architecture at Rice, Spring 1987; Cannady on pg. 8, 147776 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design News, July/Aug. 1987, pg. 14, 147775 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Architecture, August 1987; Cannady on pgs. 36-40, 147774 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Design Today, The Houston Post, 19 Sept. 1987, 147773 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - College of Environmental Design News, UC Berkeley; Cannady on pg 25, Fall 1987; 149003 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Newsletter 9, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Oct. 1987; Cannady (West Library) on pg. 7, 147771 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Newsclipping, The Tomball Sun, 8 Oct. 1987 (Church of the Good Shepherd), 147770 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 37 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1987; Cannady on pg. 69, 147768 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Invitation to a Cocktail Party, 11 Dec. 1987, 147766 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Architecture, March 1988; Cannady (American Wood Council) on pg. 26, 147763 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Architectural Record, March 1988; Cannady (West Library) on pg. 63, 147762 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Newsletter 3, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, March 1988; Cannady (Philadelphia Museum of Art) on pg. 4, 147761 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - West University Magazine, April 1988; Cannady (Village Square) on pgs. 29-30, 147758 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Newsletter 7, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, July/Aug. 1988; Cannady (Wyndham Hotel) on pg. 9, 147757 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Seven Gables Circuit, A narrative of no pretensions to accuracy or comprehensiveness from the contemporary notes of John Hart, 5-14 Aug. 1988, 147756 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Report, Texas Society of Architects, Sept. 1988; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 3, 147755 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Newsletter 8, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Sept. 1988; Cannady (hotel in Brookfield) on pg. 7, 147754 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Houston Business Journal, 12 Sept. 1988; Cannady on pg. 26, 147753 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Newsletter 9, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Oct. 1988; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 2, 147752 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - The Houston Post, "Success by Design," 17 Oct. 1988, 147751 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Houston Business Journal, 24 Oct. 1988; Cannady on pg. 23, 147750 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 38 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1988; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pgs. 42-43, 55, 147749 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Newsletter 10, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Nov./Dec. 1988; Cannady on pg. 7, 147748 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - 713: The Magazine of Contemporary Houston (cover only), Dec. 1988, 147747 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Newsletter 2, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Feb. 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 5, 147746 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Newsclipping, Houston Chronicle, 9 Feb. 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 4D, 147745 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Progressive Architecture, March 1989; Cannady (Wood Design Awards) on pg. 36, 147744 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 39 no. 2, March/April 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 15 and Blake House on pg. 22, 147743 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Architecture, April 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 34, 147742 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - College of Environmental Design News, UC Berkeley, Spring 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 27, 147741 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Design Solutions, Spring 1989; Cannady (West Library) on pgs. 53-56, 147740 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Architecture, May 1989; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 64, 147739 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - SMCA Newsletter, Fall 1989; Cannady (Children's Museum) on pg. 3, 147738 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Houston Magazine, Nov. 1989; Cannady (Wyndham Warwick Hotel) on pg. 22, 147737 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Newsletter 1, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Jan. 1990; Cannady (Children's Museum) on pg. 6, 147734 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Domain, Jan./Feb. 1990; Cannady on pg. 58, 147733 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Newsletter 4, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, April 1990; Cannady on pg. 6, 147732 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Houston Architectural Guide, 1990, 147731 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Official Register, Harvard University Graduate School of Design, 1990-1991; Cannady on pg. 85, 147728 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Building Magazine, March 1990; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 130, 147727 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Houston Chronicle, 15 April 1990; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 2H, 147726 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Design Dialogues, 26 April 1990, 147725 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Houston Post, 28 April 1990; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. E-2, 147724 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Southern Living, May 1990; Cannady (Schulte Ranch) on pg. 64, 147723 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Rice Reader, 4 June 1990; Cannady on pg. 7, 147722 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 40 no. 4, July/Aug. 1990; Cannady (West Library) on pgs. 46-47, 147721 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Architecture, Nov. 1990; Cannady (West Library) on pg. 59, 147720 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 40 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1990; Cannady (Tatlici Villa) on pg. 45, 147719 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Houston Post, 23 May 1991; Cannady (House in Shadyside) on pg. H-1, 147716 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter 10, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Nov./Dec. 1991; Cannady on pg. 7, 147715 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Texas Architect, July/Aug. 1991; Cannady (Children's Museum) on pg. 10, 147714 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - South Main Center Association Newsletter, Fall 1991; Cannady (Children's Museum) on pg. 6, 147713 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - R.O. Magazine, December 1991; Cannady on pg. 46, 147712 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Domestic Project, recent works by architects teaching at Rice, 1992, 147711 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Alumni/ae Directory, Graduate School of Design, Harvard University, 1992, 147710 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects, Houston Chapter, March 1992; Cannady on pg. 13, 147708 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Process: Architecture, May 1992; Hidiv Beldisi Villas on pg. 108, 147707 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Texas Architect, May/June 1992; Cannady (House in Shadyside) on pg. 49, 147706 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Houston Business Journal, 15 June 1992; Cannady (Julia C. Hester House) on pg. 42, 147705 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Official Register, Graduate School of Design, Harvard University, 1992-1993, 147704 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - "Back to School: Perspective on Architectural Education," Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Sept. 1992; Cannady as moderator, 147703 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Newsclipping, "The Edifice Complex," The Houston Post, 20 Dec. 1992, 147702 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Graduate School of Design News, Harvard University, Winter/Spring 1993, 147700 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects/Houston, Jan. 1993; Cannady on pg. 1, 147699 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - College of Environmental Design News, UC Berkeley, Spring 1993; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pg. 29, 147698 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Newsclipping, Houston Chronicle, 22 May 1993; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pg. B-1, 147697 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Graduate School of Design News, Harvard University, Summer 1993; Cannady on pg. 58, 147696 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Neartown Business Alliance, Sept. 1993; Cannady on pg. 1, 147695 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - R.O. Magazine, October 1993; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pgs. 12-14, 147694 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - The Official Register, Graduate School of Design, Harvard University, 1993-1994, 147693 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - The Face Book, Rice School of Architecture, 1993-1994, 147692 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Rice Design Alliance, "Best Laid Plans," 1994; Cannady on pg. 20, 147691 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Insegnare l'architettura, Maria Vegeto, 1994; Cannady on pg. 103, 147690 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Invitation, Holiday Reception and Concert, 1994, 147689 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Graduate School of Design News, Harvard University, Winter/Spring 1994, 147688 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, July/Aug. 1994; Cannady on pg. 5, 147687 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Rice School of Architecture News, Fall 1994, 147686 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Cite, The Architecture & Design Review of Houston, Fall 1994/Winter 1995, 147685 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Newsclipping, Houston Business Journal, Nov. 11-17, 1994, 147684 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - 21st Galveston Historic Homes Tour, 1995, 147682 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, April 1995; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pg. 8, 147680 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Houston Chronicle, 8 April 1995; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pg. C-1, 147679 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Texas Architect, May/June 1995; Cannady (Northern Trust Bank) on pg. 24, 147678 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Sept. 1995; Cannady (E.B. Cape Center) on pg. 11, 147677 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - College of Environmental Design, UC Berkeley, Fall 1995; Cannady (E.B. Cape Center) on pgs. 34-35, 147676 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Cite, The Architecture and Design Review of Houston, Fall 1995-Winter 1996; Cannady on pgs. 38-39, 147675 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - New York New Heights, A Tribute to the American Iron Worker, photographs by Burhan Dogancay, c. 1996, 147674 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Southern Living, Feb. 1996; Cannady on pg. 68, 147672 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, March 1996; Cannady on pg. 5, 147670 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Car Collector & Car Classics, March 1996, David Taylor Classics Car Museum on pgs. 58-63, 147669 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - The New York Times, Week in Review, 3 March 1996; Cannady on pg. 4, 147668 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Newsclipping, Houston Chronicle, 31 March 1996; Cannady (David Taylor Classic Car Museum) on pg. 12, 147667 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Fort Bend Lifestyle, April 1996, 147666 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, April 1996; Cannady (David Taylor Classics Car Museum) on pg. 9, 147665 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Celebrate Architecture, April 1996; Cannady award for design of David Taylor Classics Car Museum, 147664 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - TSA Checkset, Newsletter of the Texas Society of Architects, April 1996; Cannady on pg. 6, 147663 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, May 1996; Cannady on pg. 9, 147661 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Texas Architect, May/June 1996; Cannady (David Taylor Classics Car Museum) on pg. 15, 147660 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - CARC, The newsletter of Texas A&M University's College of Architecture, Summer 1996; Cannady on pg. 4, 147659 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Graduate School of Design News, Harvard University, Fall 1996, 147658 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - AIArchitect, The Newspaper of America's Community of Architects, Oct. 1996, 147657 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Houston Business Journal, Nov. 15-21, 1996, 147654 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - College of Environmental Design News, UC Berkeley, Fall 1996; Cannady on pg. 36, 147656 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Lord of the Streets Episcopal Church Newsletter, Fall 1996/Winter 1997; Cannady on pg. 1, 147655 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Home Plan Ideas, Winter 1996, with related Cannady correspondence, 147652 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Rice Design Alliance, Houston Works, 1997; Cannady on pg. 80, 147650 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Pinnacle Oaks Houston Real Estate, c. 1997; Round Top property on pg. 21, 147649 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Jan. 1997; Cannady on pg. 10, 147646 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - School of Continuing Studies, Rice University, Spring 1997; Cannady on pg. 5, 147645 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Cite, The Architecture and Design Review of Houston, Spring 1997, 147644 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Sallyport, Spring 1997; Cannady on pg. 17, 147643 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Society of Design Administration, Greater Houston Chapter, an affiliate of the American Institute of Architects, 30 June 1997; Cannady on pg. 1, 147640 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, July/Aug. 1997; Cannady on pg. 14, 147639 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Houston Chronicle, 12 July 1997; Cannady on pg. 3-D, 147638 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Texas Architect, Nov./Dec. 1997, E.B. Cape Center for Public Works Excellence, 147637 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Annual Report, City of Port Arthur - article: Students Study Pleasure Isle Development, March 27, 1966; 149009 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Series IV: Certificates, personal, and oversize, 149038
  - Certificate of Merit - Marine Corps School, 1957; 149050 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - University of California - Berkeley, 1961; 149051 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - US Marine Corps - Honorable Discharge, 1962; 149115 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AIA Membership, 1965; 149116 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Council of Architectural Registration Boards, 1975; 149052 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Missouri Board for Architects, Professional Engineers and Land Surveyors - Registered Architect, 1984; 149054 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - State of Texas - Interior Designer authorization, 1993; 149053 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Suits: The Clothes Make the Man - The Art Guys with Todd Oldham (signed book with letter), 149055 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Chapels for Tomorrow, 1960; 149056 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lee Estate - land development analysis, April 1971; 149057 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Newhoff Industries - site location analysis, April 1971; 149058 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hosanna - New Town in Town, Fairfax VA, c. 1972; 149059 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Building Ideas with page on Cannady House, Spring/Summer 1975; 149060 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Cannady scans - A&E, September 2, 2011; 149061 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Mix up, Tenneco Downtown Properties Study, 1966-1967; 149071 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Goodyear Blimport, Spring TX and Rome Italy, 1968; 149062 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Ormsby County High School, Carson City NV, 1968; 149063 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Ormsby County High School, Carson City NV, 1968; 149064 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Arizona State University, Litchfield AZ, 1968-1969; 149065 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - KJCDC, 1968-1969; 149066 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - KJCDC, 1968-1969; 149067 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - KJCDC, 1968-1969; 149068 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - US Public Health Hospital, Galveston TX, 1968-1969; 149069 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Caudill Rowlett Scott work cards - Kern County Junior College, Ridgecrest CA, 1969; 149070 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Omniplan work cards - Hosanna, New Town, Fairfax Co. VA, 1971; 149072 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Omniplan work cards - Misc. Projects, 149073 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - AIArchitect - v. 5, June 1997 - May 1998; 149100 (Box 12)
  - AIArchitect - v. 5, May 1998; 149101 (Box 12)
  - AIArchitect - v. 5, August 1998; 149102 (Box 12)
  - AIArchitect - v. 6, June 1999; 149099 (Box 12)
  - Skyline - The Architecture and Design Review, November 1981; 149098 (Box 12)
  - Harvard University - Masters of Architecture, 1962; 149114 (Box 12)
  - Texas Board of Architectural Examiners - Architect, 1965; 149113 (Box 12)
  - AIA - Fellow, 1979; 149112 (Box 12)
  - Board of Architectural Examiners Louisiana - Architect, 1983; 149111 (Box 12)
  - Award - The National Conference on Religious Architecture Honor Award for Excellence in Design to the St. Barnabas Episcopal Church, 1971; 149097 (Box 12)
  - Award - Architectural Record Award of Excellence for House Design presented to William T. Cannady for his own house, c. 1973; 149078 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for David A. Crane Residence, Houston TX, c. 1974; 149095 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Brochstein Residence, Houston TX, c. 1975; 149096 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Lovett Square, Houston TX, c. 1979; 149094 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Sunset Terrace, Houston TX, c. 1979; 149093 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Eastwood Park, Houston TX, c. 1980; 149092 (Box 12)
  - Award - AIA Houston and the Municipal Art Commission present an award of distinguished achievement to Eastwood Park, c. 1982; 149079 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Cannady Ranch, Walhalla TX, c. 1982; 149091 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Sid W. Richardson Institute for Preventive Medicine, Houston TX, c. 1983; 149089 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Village Square, Houston TX, c. 1985; 149090 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Church of the Good Shepherd, Tomball TX, c. 1985; 149088 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award in Recognition of Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Schulte Ranch, Round Top TX, c. 1988; 149087 (Box 12)
  - Award - Wood Design Merit Award for Schulte Ranch, 1988; 149086 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Cannady residence, Houston TX, undated; 149084 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Award of Merit for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Children's Mental Health Services of Houston, undated; 149085 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Honor Award for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for the Commons Town Houses, Houston TX, undated; 149083 (Box 12)
  - Award - Texas Society of Architects - Award of Merit for Outstanding Architectural Design and Achievement for Walker's Mark Townhouses, Houston TX, undated; 149080 (Box 12)
  - Cannady Drawing - Juan R. Avila, 1957; 149077 (Box 12)
  - Lovett Square information cards, 149081 (Box 12)
  - Sketches - unnamed house, undated; 149076 (Box 12)
  - Sketches - Brochstein House, c. 1972; 149075 (Box 12)
  - Sketches - Papadeaux's Restaurant, Richmond Blvd. (21 sheets), 163005 (Box 12)
  - Texas A&M fourth year design studio - veterinary clinic and house, 1960; 149074 (Box 12)
  - Photograph - Lovett Square, 163000 (Box 12)
  - Photograph - 2401-03 Sunset Blvd, 163001 (Box 12)
  - Photograph - Indian Trail, Memorial, 163003 (Box 12)
  - Bid set and Construction set for new residence for Steven and Elizabeth Bricker, September 13, 2010, November 8, 2010; 171285 (Box 13)
  - Proposed Lilly Ice Cream plant, Bryan, TX, Dec. 3, 1959; 172085 (Box 13)
  - Parking Study: 2000-2010, Rice University, 171294 (Box 13)
  - Project Portfolio, 171295 (Box 13)
  - Four Houses galley proof, n.d. and draft, February 17, 2014; 171296 (Box 13)
  - Cite, A Publication of the Rice Design Alliance, Summer 2005; 171298 (Box 13)
  - Cite, A Publication of the Rice Design Alliance, Spring 2006; 171299 (Box 13)
  - Houston House & Culture, vol. 7, no. 1, January 2000; 171301 (Box 13)
  - Texas Medical Center. 50 year master plan, 1999; 172211
  - Augusta Oaks Townhomes, n.d.; 172212 (Box 13)
  - University of Miami. Program Schematic drawings, parts 1 and 2, November 1962; 172213 (Box 13)
  - Walker's Mark plans, n.d.; 172214 (Box 13)
  - Palisades Site evaluation, n.d.; 172215 (Box 13)
  - Benjamin Franklin Savings prototype signage, June 12, 1981; 172216 (Box 13)
  - Mid-Main Mixed Use Landscape Design Review, January 27, 2014; Floor plans, January 7, 2014, 179501 (Box 13)
  - New retail center, 6135 Kirby Drive, set of drawings, February 5, 1992; 171305 (Box 14)
  - 5 mounted drawings of new retail center, 6135 Kirby Drive, 171307 (Box 14)
  - Houston Area Center II, Bricker & Cannady, Architects, November 6, 2001; 171311 (Box 14)
  - University of Houston Recreation Center, Majestic Springs project, Bricker & Cannady, Architects, May 29, 2001; 171315 (Box 14)
  - Macy's at Galleria, Houston, February 19, 1999; 171324 (Box 14)
  - Menil Foundation Properties Study, 171326 (Box 14)
  - New Wedge Tower sketches, 171328 (Box 14)
  - University of Houston Boundary Survey, 171329 (Box 14)
  - William T. Cannady and Associates Project Examples, 171331 (Box 14)
  - Color Studio Houses, 171332 (Box 14)
- Series V: Addendum I, 170081
  - Undergraduate and Graduate work, 1956-1962; 170480
    - Texas A&M. Oceanography & Meteorology school for Texas A&M drawing. Ten-week problem., 172217 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Texas A&M. Lights for living project, 172218 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Texas A&M. Small animal clinic project, 172219 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Texas A&M. House for tile competition, 172220 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Texas A&M. 7-11 store, working drawings, 172224 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Texas A&M. Tennis & swim center, 172226 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Texas A&M. Miscellaneous sketches, 172225 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Texas A&M. Texas A&M Pavilion, 172227 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Texas A&M. Train station., 172228 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Texas A&M. Small chapel., 172229 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Texas A&M. Boston City Hall competition, 1961; 172230 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Texas A&M. Museum display panel, 172231 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Texas A&M. Twenty-foot cube house., 172232 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Texas A&M. Plant Science Building for Texas A&M., December 1959; 172233 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Texas A&M. Drive-in bank, 172295 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Texas A&M. Museum of Fine Arts, 172296 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Texas A&M. Garden apartments, 172297 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Texas A&M. Art contest and miscellaneous drawings, 1959; 172300 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Texas A&M. Small building design, 1959; 172302 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Texas A&M. Foster City, CA town center, 1960; 172304 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Texas A&M. Miscellaneous drawings, 1956-60; 172314 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - University of California-Berkeley. Landscape project, Spring 1961; 172305 (Box 15, Folder 22)